import 'package:word_quiz/model/parental_gate_data.dart';

const zettaiReido = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'ぜったいれいど',
  correct: '絶対零度',
  answerList: [
    '絶対零度',
    '亜空切断',
    '空前絶後',
    '絶対音感',
  ],
);

const namiNori = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'なみのり',
  correct: '波乗り',
  answerList: [
    '波乗り',
    '海乗り',
    '並の力',
    '大地の力',
  ],
);

const jikoSaisei = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'じこさいせい',
  correct: '自己再生',
  answerList: [
    '自己再生',
    '輪廻転生',
    '生々流転',
    '自然再生',
  ],
);

const hakaiKosen = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'はかいこうせん',
  correct: '破壊光線',
  answerList: [
    '破壊光線',
    '必殺前歯',
    '亜空切断',
    '我武者羅',
  ],
);

const jitensha = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'じてんしゃ',
  correct: '自転車',
  answerList: [
    '自転車',
    '荷車',
    '飛行機',
    '機関車',
  ],
);

const konjo = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'こんじょう',
  correct: '根性',
  answerList: [
    '根性',
    '大根',
    '岩石',
    '石頭',
  ],
);

const kairiki = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'かいりき',
  correct: '怪力',
  answerList: [
    '怪龍',
    '怪力',
    '白龍',
    '小龍',
  ],
);

const daiMonji = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'だいもんじ',
  correct: '大文字',
  answerList: [
    '大文字',
    '火炎放射',
    '炎武王',
    '鬼火',
  ],
);

const ishiAtama = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'いしあたま',
  correct: '石頭',
  answerList: [
    '石頭',
    '岩石',
    '葉緑素',
    '根性',
  ],
);

const mizuDeppou = ParentalGateData(
  question: 'みずでっぽう',
  correct: '水鉄砲',
  answerList: [
    '水鉄砲',
    '岩雪崩',
    '大文字',
    '火炎放射',
  ],
);

final parentalGateList = [
  zettaiReido,
  namiNori,
  jikoSaisei,
  hakaiKosen,
  jitensha,
  konjo,
  kairiki,
  daiMonji,
  ishiAtama,
  mizuDeppou
];
